<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-08-25T13:01:11+02:00</updated><id>https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//feed.xml</id><title type="html">Radwan’s Thoughts</title><subtitle>I dunno.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">First Post</title><link href="https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//example/2021/08/24/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Post" /><published>2021-08-24T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-08-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//example/2021/08/24/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//example/2021/08/24/first-post.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;welcome-message&quot;&gt;Welcome Message!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h2 id=&quot;through-me-you-go-into-a-city-of-weeping-through-me-you-go-into-eternal-pain-through-me-you-go-amongst-the-lost-people&quot;&gt;Through me you go into a city of weeping; through me you go into eternal pain; through me you go amongst the lost people&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dante Alighieri, The Inferno&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;let-me-flex-a-lil-bit&quot;&gt;Let me flex a lil bit&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I coded this blog becasue simply i was bored, and I wanted a blog. So in less than an hour I got this up and running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;technical-details&quot;&gt;Technical Details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hosted by Github Pages, because I don’t wanna pay for a crappy host that I won’t use anyway, and the “Github.io” domain sits the nerdy theme for the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;just-another-text&quot;&gt;Just another text&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, you got it now. I’m run outta ideas to write. Bye!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="example" /><summary type="html">Welcome Message! Through me you go into a city of weeping; through me you go into eternal pain; through me you go amongst the lost people Dante Alighieri, The Inferno</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Moment Before Dying</title><link href="https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//stories/2021/08/24/a-moment-before-dying.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Moment Before Dying" /><published>2021-08-24T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-08-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//stories/2021/08/24/a-moment-before-dying</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://radwan43.github.io/Radwan43//stories/2021/08/24/a-moment-before-dying.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;there-is-a-moment-immediately-before-life-becomes-no-longer-worth-living-when-the-world-appears-to-slow-down-and-all-its-myriad-details-suddenly-become-brightly-achingly-apparent&quot;&gt;There is a moment, immediately before life becomes no longer worth living when the world appears to slow down and all its myriad details suddenly become brightly, achingly apparent.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For our hero, it was after he realized that despite having everything anyone would wish, he didn’t get anything he wanted. It was when he realized that whom he cared for, never cared for him. He kept the last years of his life chasing fake dreams, and ghosts who only existed in his head. Although he had the image of someone who don’t give a fuck, he gave. He wasn’t the heartless he tried to be, it was just a part of the perfect person he wanted to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day he killed himself, he woke up alone, as usual. He tried to remember his dreams as he was happy there. He woke up to do his same daily routines. He finished work and went on a long walk in his favorite place, but everything wasn’t the same. The streets he walked hundreds of times felt different and strange, he doubted every step he took, he even doubted if he’s entering the right home. He was a stranger in a world that wasn’t his.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day he killed himself, his message still unread, his voice still unheard, he didn’t get the reply he waited for. The day he killed himself, he got sick of everything. The day he killed himself he stopped trying, he decided to end everything, peacefully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day he killed himself, he grabbed a rope, and died in his apartment, in the same way he lived, alone.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html">There is a moment, immediately before life becomes no longer worth living when the world appears to slow down and all its myriad details suddenly become brightly, achingly apparent. For our hero, it was after he realized that despite having everything anyone would wish, he didn’t get anything he wanted. It was when he realized that whom he cared for, never cared for him. He kept the last years of his life chasing fake dreams, and ghosts who only existed in his head. Although he had the image of someone who don’t give a fuck, he gave. He wasn’t the heartless he tried to be, it was just a part of the perfect person he wanted to be.</summary></entry></feed>